<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="configuration.xsl"?>
<configuration>
  <property>
    <name>http.agent.name</name>
    <value>ApacheNutchForTypo3</value>
    <description>
      HTTP 'User-Agent' request header. MUST NOT be empty -
      please set this to a single word uniquely related to your organization.
    </description>
  </property>

  <property>
    <name>http.robots.agents</name>
    <value>ApacheNutchForTypo3,*</value>
    <description>The agent strings we'll look for in robots.txt files,
    comma-separated, in decreasing order of precedence. You should
    put the value of http.agent.name as the first agent name, and keep the
    default * at the end of the list. E.g.: BlurflDev,Blurfl,*
    </description>
  </property>

  <property>
    <name>plugin.includes</name>
    <value>protocol-http|urlfilter-regex|parse-(html|tika)|index-(basic|anchor|static)|indexer-solr|urlnormalizer-(pass|regex|basic)|language-identifier|urlmeta|typo3-(accessrootline|base|index-keywords|parse-keywords|sitehash|uid|endtime)</value>
    <description>
      Regular expression naming plugin directory names to
      include.  Any plugin not matching this expression is excluded.
      In any case you need at least include the nutch-extensionpoints plugin. By
      default Nutch includes crawling just HTML and plain text via HTTP,
      and basic indexing and search plugins. In order to use HTTPS please enable
      protocol-httpclient, but be aware of possible intermittent problems with the
      underlying commons-httpclient library.
    </description>
  </property>

  <property>
    <name>db.ignore.external.links</name>
    <value>true</value>
    <description>
      If true, outlinks leading from a page to external hosts
      will be ignored. This is an effective way to limit the crawl to include
      only initially injected hosts, without creating complex URLFilters.
  </description>
  </property>

  <property>
    <name>typo3.baseUrl</name>
    <value>http://www.example.com</value>
    <description>
      URL to the website with the TYPO3 installation
    </description>
  </property>

  <property>
    <name>typo3.api.key</name>
    <value></value>
    <description>
      Api Key for the SiteHash Api.
      Can be found in your TYPO3 installation backend in the Search Module at the bottom.
    </description>
  </property>

  <property>
    <name>typo3.access.rootline</name>
    <value>c:0</value>
    <description>
      Access Rootline to be indexed for the crawled pages.
    </description>
  </property>

  <!-- optional HTML Parser properties -->
  <!-- Added by NUTCH-585 https://issues.apache.org/jira/secure/attachment/12494949/nutch-585-excludeNodes.patch -->
  <property>
    <name>parser.html.NodesToExclude</name>
    <value></value>
    <description>
      A list of nodes whose content will not be indexed separated by "|".
      Use this to tell the HTML parser to ignore, for example, site navigation text.

      Each node has three elements, separated by semi-colon:
      the first one is the tag name,
      the second one the attribute name,
      the third one the value of the attribute.

      Example: table;summary;header|div;id;navigation

      Note that nodes with these attributes, and their children, will be
      silently ignored by the parser so verify the indexed content
      with Luke to confirm results.
    </description>
  </property>

  <property>
    <name>typo3.endtime</name>
    <value>2030-01-01T00:00:00+0000</value>
    <description>
      Adds an endtime value for the Solr documents.
      You can set a static date in this format: 2020-01-01T00:00:00+0000
      You can also set a long value to add the given number of
      milliseconds to the current date, e.g. 1209600000 for two weeks.
    </description>
  </property>

</configuration>
